Now we're going to learn the lift up with your second hand.
If you hoop to the left, your second hand is your left hand.
If you hoop to the right, your second hand is your right hand.
Starting at the waist, look down, watch the hoop.
As the hoop swings around to the front of your body, you're going to take your second hand, dip it in the hoop, grab the hoop as if you're shaking someone's hand, turn with the hoop, and lift it up.
Let's get a little bit more detailed.
At the waist, your second hand dips into the hoop, grab the hoop, and lift it up all the way up into lasso over the head.
There's one tricky movement that happens with the hand.
As you lift up, the hoop is going to roll over your thumb and into the palm of your hand.
It's a little bit tricky.
Really try to push the hoop forward and keep it in that strong horizontal plane above your head.
Let's try it again.
Take the hoop to the waist, start hooping in your comfortable direction, take the second hand, notice when the hoops create an opening in front of your body.
Hands dips into the hoop like you're shaking someone's hand, lift, and turn.
Bring the hoop up into lasso.
Turning is really important in this move.
One more time.
Hooping at the waist, dipping the hand in, turning, spiraling all the way up into lasso with the second hand.
Nice job.